Help me. He's going to kill me.
What did mommy say?
I don't really understand
anymore.
Mom, are you okay?
Don't pressure her.
Why are you interfering?
How dare you talk to me
like that?
Stop this!
I'm worried about Ma'am Rebecca.
If Rebecca really has amnesia,
her memory must not return.
You think this could be her?
The video is too unclear.
If you want to go
see your friend, go.
Tell him we'll meet,
even Andrew will come too.
Okay, I'm on my way.
That's our target.
Joey, wait a minute, okay?
- Andrew, what's that?
- Sorry, I thought there was...
Andrew, what's going on?
Why, Joey? What happened?
[STAMMERS]
He's not answering, but it seems
something bad happened to him.
Come on, get in.
Andrew?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLACKING AND CLANKING]
[PETER GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING]
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
His car is here!
Where...
- Andrew!
Where is he!
Andrew!
Let's split up!
Be careful!
Be careful too!
- Andrew!
What do you want? Money?
I don't need your money.
We came here for you.
Let's go!
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUDDING AND GRUNTING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew!
Bro, someone's here! Let's go!
Boss said just teach him
a lesson!
- Don't kill him! Come on!
- Andrew!
- Bro, let's go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew! Andrew!
Help! Peter!
Peter, help!
Call...
Call an ambulance, quick!
Andrew...
Andrew! Andrew! Andrew!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Get the car.
Where are we going, Boss?
We'll follow Jin Ho.
I'm going to deal with his
"so-called friend."
[PHONE CHIMES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
Yvette...
Looks like Andrew won't be
coming back.
Maybe I should just go home.
It's up to you.
Sorry if Andrew left you.
You wasted your time.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
It's okay.
At least I visited
Mommy Rebecca.
Who are you again?
I'm Zoey.
I was your favorite
ex-girlfriend of Andrew's.
His ex?
[PHONE RINGING]
Andrew, where are you?
This is Joey.
Joey?
We need to take Andrew
to the hospital.
Why? What happened to Andrew?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
Jin Ho!
Why are you still here?
I thought you were going
to meet your friend.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
It's cancelled.
No meeting tonight.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AMBULANCE SIREN BLARES]
- Andrew!
- What happened to him?
We found him being attacked
by two men!
Who?
We didn't see their faces
because they were wearing
helmets.
Before we could get there,
the two men left.
Andrew, are you...
Sir...
Sir, wake up.
You'll be intubated
if you don't speak.
- What's your name?
- Andrew...
Sir...
- Andrew!
Sir, what's your name?
Andrew, wake up.
Andrew.
So, his name is Andrew?
Yes, it's Andrew, Doc.
Sorry.
You need to stay out.
Yvette...
Joey, maybe it's better
if we go home.
The way Zoey is looking at us,
it's like she'll eat us alive.
And your parents
might scold you.
Because we said
we'd just eat out.
Peter, if you want to go home,
then go.
But I won't leave
until Andrew is okay.
But I won't leave you too.
And of course,
Andrew is our friend too.
And it seems you two became
really close while I was away...
You cried so hard
over what happened to him.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Peter, Andrew is important
to me.
Due to everything
we've been through.
So, I hope he recovers.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
His head wound isn't too deep,
Ma'am.
But it still needs stitches.
The patient has many bruises.
But according to the CT scan,
there's no major problem.
No skull fracture, nothing else.
Do everything, Doc,
to make my brother better.
Of course, Ma'am.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
But we'll have to wait for him
to fully wake up.
For now, we'll admit the patient
and then, we'll observe.
Thank you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew...
Who did this to you?
They were wearing helmets,
so I didn't see their faces.
You know, if you hadn't come,
we might have found Andrew dead.
They beat him up so badly.
Who could those animals be?
You know, I have an idea
who did this.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Who?
Only one person knew
we were going there.
I'm sure he suspected
we'd confront him.
Jin Ho?
Joey, no, that's unlikely.
It seems impossible.
Jin Ho wouldn't do this to us.
If not him, then who?
Relax, Hon.
At least Andrew got medical
attention.
He'll be okay.
I'm on my way to the hospital.
I'll be with you soon.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Your boys did well,
unlike the failed attempt
on Rebecca's life.
[SCOFFS]
You've had it
with your brother-in-law.
You didn't let him off the hook.
He's too cocky.
That show-off learned
his lesson.
And he's not the only one
I taught a lesson to
with what I did.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, take me to my son,
please.
Did you get closer to Andrew?
You don't even remember him
being your son,
now your concern for him
is this much?
Because he's always the one
watching over me here.
I got used to him.
And, Mom,
Andrew is resting so let's visit
him tomorrow, okay?
And you should rest too.
You also need to rest.
Please.
Okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Hon, maybe you should rest too.
I'm sure you're tired
from everything that happened.
If you want,
I'll watch over mom.
No, it's okay.
Besides, I'll talk to the police
downstairs
about what happened to Andrew.
Honestly, I have no idea
who did this to my brother.
We both know Andrew has done
many exposés,
so lots of people are angry
with him.
Maybe someone got offended
and retaliated.
What they did to Andrew
was too much.
What? They were just going
to kill my brother?
Well, that should serve
as a lesson to your brother.
He should be careful
who he crosses next time.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
After that,
they immediately left.
Why did they suddenly back out?
I don't know either.
Do you have any idea
who would do this?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am Yvette! Excuse me.
Ma'am Yvette...
Yvette,
- how's Andrew?
- Has he woken up?
Well, not yet, but he's been
returned to the private room.
- Can I see him?
- Are visitors allowed?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
How dare you.
You have no right to see Andrew
because you're the reason
for all of this!
What?
Andrew and I should have been
together,
but you called him
and brought him
to that godforsaken place
where he was attacked.
I didn't know that
would happen to him.
Of course!
Because you don't think
things through.
You act on impulse,
and then everyone around you
gets hurt!
And where were you?
Why was Andrew
the only one beaten?
Where were you when he was being
attacked?
Wait...
If you're going to fight,
just go home.
I can't handle any more stress,
okay?
And Andrew doesn't need this.
You heard Yvette.
Go, leave now!
Zoey...
you too.
We've had enough for tonight,
okay? We don't deserve this.
So, please go.
Let's go, Joey. Let's go home.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll go ahead.
Andrew is still unconscious
when we left the hospital.
I'm really worried
about him now.
Now, you're worried?
Didn't I tell you
not to interfere in my
investigation of Jin Ho?
Why are you walking around
on your own?
What if you got dragged into it?
I was with Joey.
You too!
Instead of stopping her,
you allowed it.
What if something happened
to my daughter?
What would you do?
I'm sorry, Uncle Miguel.
I'm sorry, Dad.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's enough, Miguel.
Maybe now you've learned
your lesson?
It's my fault, Mom.
Because of me, Andrew got hurt.
This wouldn't have happened
to him.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE KEYS CLICKING]
Your friends
must be really special
for you to be this upset.
Yeah.
I was really looking forward
to seeing them.
Special, indeed.
Who are these friends
of yours anyway?
Can you tell me more about them?
I just met them
while I was looking for you.
They were kind to me.
I really felt that I was part
of their group.
I'm not used to having a friend.
I'm more used to competing.
But you don't have to prove
anything to me
because you're my friend.
Jin Ho! Are you okay?
I just wanted to give that
to you.
So that wherever you are,
you never forget that you have
friends.
But I ghosted them
when I found you.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
That's it?
Aren't you going to tell me
anything more important?
Like their names
or where they're from?
You won't be interested.
They're just normal people,
not from our world.
[SIGHS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
I should return this to you.
Do you know this is for you?
Lucky you picked it up.
I don't think luck is the word.
- What?
- Fate.
It was destined...
to end up with me.
Dear...
Mom?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Because I'm still worried.
Do you want to say...
or tell me something
about Andrew?
What would I say, Mom?
You know, my child...
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
when your father
was courting me,
I played hard to get.
I didn't admit to him
what I really felt.
Really, Mom?
Yes.
Then one day he got hurt
on duty.
That's when...
That's when I really realized
I loved him.
Because...
it hurt me so much to see him
suffering.
Sorry, Mom.
I just don't understand
what I'm feeling.
It's my first time feeling this.
That's okay, dear.
You don't have to be sure
right away.
What's important is,
always remember,
whatever you want to say
or share...
I'm here, I'll listen to you.
And I promise...
I won't judge you.
Thank you, Mom.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCK ON THE DOOR]
Good morning, Yvette.
How is Andrew?
He's stable, but still resting.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Yvette...
I'm really sorry about
what happened last night.
I know it's wrong
to make accusations,
but I just feel bad
about what happened.
I understand.
Don't worry about it anymore.
He's just too important to me.
And you, his whole family.
So, if you'll allow me, Yvette,
I'll watch over Andrew.
You already have too much
on your plate.
Thank you.
I feel...
I feel better if...
I personally know the one
watching over him.
And I've known you for years.
And I think...
Andrew will be so happy to see
you here when he wakes up.
You being a law enforcer
makes me more confident
for Andrew's safety.
I'm just afraid the person who
did this to him might come back.
Yvette,
if you're worried about that,
I have a proposal.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What if Zoey is inside?
You might end up fighting.
I don't care what
that Zoey says.
She can say whatever she wants.
We're here to see Andrew.
Okay, but you promised.
Stay calm.
Of course.
That's the room.
Sir...
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
We're just visiting
Andrew Dizon.
No visitors allowed.
It's okay, Sir.
We're Andrew's friends.
Is Ma'am Yvette there?
I'm Joey Delgado.
We're Andrew's friends.
We won't cause trouble.
We'll just visit him.
Sorry.
Strict orders from Ma'am Zoey.
No one can enter.
Zoey? So, she's the one watching
Andrew?
So, Zoey is inside?
Peter...
Hey, Zoey, come out!
- Peter!
- Face us! Zoey!
Hey, Zoey, come out here! Zoey!
Don't cause trouble here.
[CLAMORING]
Zoey!
You are at the hospital.
Don't cause trouble!
Zoey, come out!
He's so stubborn.
I'm sure Joey is with him,
that's why he's making
a scene outside.
Andrew, don't worry.
I'll take care of it, okay?
Just rest.
I'll make sure that woman
won't bother you again.
[UNEASY MUSIC]
- Zoey!
- Don't cause trouble here.
Zoey, come out!
- Sir.
- Peter!
Go on, I'll handle this.
Let's talk calmly, no shouting.
Is that okay?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
We don't have anything
to talk about.
We just want to visit Andrew.
Andrew's security is tight
because someone attempted
to take his life.
So, visitors must be limited.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Zoey, we don't want trouble.
We just want to check on Andrew.
Is that it?
Well, he's fine.
He's safe now.
He's resting to recover
and get his strength back.
Then why does it seem like you
don't want to show him to us?
Like you're hiding him.
And you...
Why are you forcing yourself
to see Andrew?
For what?
To get attention?
Come on, Joey.
I know your strategy.
You stick close to Andrew,
hoping he'll notice you.
You'll use every excuse
just to get into his orbit.
Why?
Because you like him, don't you?
Am I right?
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
Joey...
You're too obvious.
It's embarrassing.
You know what? I think Andrew
has noticed what you're doing,
but he's just too much
of a gentleman to call you out.
But believe me, Joey.
There's no chance Andrew will
like an immature kid like you.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
Help! Andrew!
Joey?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm telling you.
Someone wants to hurt
or kill Andrew.
You know, I'll just think that
I'm happy Andrew is awake
and recovering.
Maybe it's time to move him
somewhere more peaceful.
This is our life, Jin Ho.
You can't just walk away
from that.
I have a plan.
I'm thinking of the best thing
we can do.
Peter, we won't be reckless
this time.
Someone will help us.
[PHONE RINGING]
Jin Ho, we need your help.
We don't know who else
we can trust.
You know what?
I thought you were going to die
when I held you?